Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
- Box: 26, Folder: 18 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 25: Group Tax-Deferred Annuity Program, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
    By California Institute of Technology. Booklet 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Your retirement Annuity, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 27: Working For Caltech, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Box: 26, Folder: 19 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Policies and Procedures, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Staff Personnel Memoranda, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Box: 26, Folder: 20 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 20)
    By California Metal Trades Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Box: 26, Folder: 21 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation Plan-Operating Divisions, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
    By California Packing Corporation. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, Folder: 22 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: State Personnel Administration In TheWar Years: A Review of Acitivites During the Years 1941-1946, Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
    By California State Personnel Board. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, Folder: 23 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Western Personnel Management and Industrial Relations Directory, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
    By The California Personnel Management Association, The Western Management Association and Other Sources. With Principal Organization Listings Including Company Executives Who are Primarily Interested in This Field. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Right to Work: A Brief of the Testimony of cecil B. DeMille Before the House of Representatives Committee on Education and Labor and As Shown by Motion Picture to the 20th Pacific Coast Management Conference, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
    By Cecil B. DeMille. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Working Under the Wage-Hour Law, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
    By William B. McComb. A Stenographic Brief of an Address Given Before the 20th Pacific Coast Management Conference By William B. McComb, Administrator Wage and Hour Division, U.S. Department of Labor Washington, D.C. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Developing Trends in Labor Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
    By Rocco C. Siciliano. A Stenographic Brief of an Address given before The California Personnel management Association and the Personnel Section of The Western Management Association by Rocco C. Siciliano, Assistant Secretary of labor United States Department of Labor; No. 194. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Trends and Developments in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
    By J. J. O'Donnell. A Stenographic Brief of An Address Given Before The California Personnel Management Association and the Personnel Section of The Western Management Association by J.J. ODonnell, Peronnel & Labor Relations Manager The Lummus Company, no.216. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Labor Relations in the West Coats Maritime Industry, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
    By Harry Lundberg. No. 204. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Supplementary unemployment Pay Plans: West Coast Experiences, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
    By Neal Hammond; W. P. Bell; R. W. Evans; S. Steinhauer; Marc Johnson; J. R. Roberts; W. R. Siegel. No. 236. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: the Annual Wage Drive & Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
    By The California Personnel Management Association, The Western Management Association and Other Sources. No. 224. Item is in English.
- Box: 26, Folder: 24 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Summer Labor Institute, Miramar Hotel, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    By University of California, Berkeley. Leaflet. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Research: Community Services: Curriculum: Degrees, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    By Institute of Industrial Relations; University of California, Berkeley. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Automation, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    By Richard Bellman. Address to Council of Engineers and Scientists Organization-West. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Role of Government in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    By William M. Leiserson. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Education for Management; An Experiment in Interdisciplinary Teaching, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    By Warren H. Schmidt; Erwin M. Keithley; Arthur J. Shedlin. Research Paper no.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Industrial Relations Curriculum at UC Berkeley, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    By Industrial Relations Institute, University of California, Berkeley. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Institute of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    By Industrial Relations Institute, University of California, Los Angeles. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Institute of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    By Industrial Relations Institute, University of California. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Publications of the Institute of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: The Institute of Life Insurance, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    By The Institute of Life Insurance. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Publications of the Institute of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    By Institute of Industrial Relations; University of California. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Institute of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 13: A Progress Report of the Institute of Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    By Institute of Industrial Relations. UC B and UC LA. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Progress Report of Research and Community Services Program 1959-1960, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Item 15: Labor Arbitration and its Critics, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)
    By Benjamin Aaron. Reprinted from Labor Law Journal, September 1959. Reprint no.89. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Rating Plan Helps to Make Better Supervisors, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
    By D.D Decker. Reprint from factory Management and Maintenance, v.101:no.6 (1943:June). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Executive Self Improvement Form, Publication (Box 27, Folder 1)
    By Calumet and Hecla Consolidation Copper Co. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Employees Manual for Hourly-Paid Employees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    By Canadair. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employees Manual for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Inventions Plans for Canadair Employees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 2)
    By Canadair. Item is in English; French.
- Box: 27, Folder: 3 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Campbell Kids Welcome You, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    By Campbell Soup Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: ABC of Hand Tools, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    By Campbell Soup Company. Reprinted from 1945 General Motors pubication. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Wage and Salary Administration, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
    By Campbell Soup Company. Descriptions of Operations/ Job Titles and Definitions. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Employment of Management Trainees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Let TAP help you get Ahead; Campbell's Tuition Aid Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Your Campbell Career; A handbook for employees of the General Office, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: So YOU are a warehouser, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Good Food Handling Practices, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Scholarship Program for Children of Employees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Safety and Audit Checklist, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Safety Briefing for New Employees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Campbell Soups Employee Benefit Plans for Regular Full-time Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Box: 27, Folder: 4 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Industrial relations and Disputes Investigation Regulations, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By Canada Department of Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Rules of Procedure of The Canada Labour Relations Board, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: A Survey Report on Labour Education in Canada carried out during the fall and winter, 1949-50, Publication (Box 27, Folder 4)
    By David Smith. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 5 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Rules of Procedure of the Canada Labour Relations Board, Publication (Box 27, Folder 5)
    By Canada Labour Relations Board. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 6 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Information Circular, Publication (Box 27, Folder 6)
    By Canadian General Electric Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 7 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constituion Governing Action and Procedure of Canadian National Railways Joint Co-Operative Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    By Canadian National Railways. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Apprenticeship Program of the Canadian National Railways, Publication (Box 27, Folder 7)
    By Bureau of Training, Apprentice-Training Service. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 8 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Employee-Employer Relations Under Unionized Conditions, Publication (Box 27, Folder 8)
    By Samuel R. Robb. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 9 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Plant Operations: A Description of the Manufacturing process For New Employees In The Production Dept., Publication (Box 27, Folder 9)
    By The Calvert Distilling Co. Education Dept. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 10 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Group life and Disability Insurance Plan for Salaried Employees of he Carborundum Company, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
    By Carborundum Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Group Medical insurance Plan for Salaried Employees of The Carborundum Company, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Retirement Plan For Salaried Employees of the Carborundum Company, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: The Romance of Carborundum, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Paying Higher Wages to Reduce Costs, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Voluntary Group Accident Plan For Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Performance Appraisal Program: Supervisory and Professional Personnel, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Performance Appraisal Program: Office and Laboratory Personnel, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Benefit Summary- Salaried Employees Applicable To Employees Earning $24,000 or Hihger Annually, Publication (Box 27, Folder 10)
    By Carborundum Company. 2 Copies. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 11 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Carborundum Manual, Publication (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Box: 27, Folder: 12 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Benefits, Publication (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Box: 27, Folder: 13 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By Carnation Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Employee Progress Record, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Carnation Company, Where There's an Exciting Future for You..., Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By Carnation Company. Recruitment folder. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Grocery Products Marketing Organization, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By Carnation Company. Management Development Program. In recruitment folder. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Evaporated Division, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Instant Products Division, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Albers Milling Company Production Department, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Engineering Department, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Fresh Milk and Ice Cream Division, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By Carnation Company. In recruitment folder. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Carnation Research Laboratories, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Metal Cans From Carnation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: Group Life Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Hospital And Disability Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: Retirement Plan Number One, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: Hospital Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: Your Carnation Career, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 18: Letter to C. C. Balderston, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By Freda A. Tilden. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Safety Committee, Its Organization And Duties, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 20: Safety News, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By General Safety Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Protection For You and Yours, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By The Travelers Insurance Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Protection for You and Yours: Group Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By Carnation Company; The Travelers Insurance Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Carnation opportunities, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 24: Group Insurance Instructions, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 25: Your Equity In A Famous Name, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 26: Opportunities in Sales, Manufacturing, Acounting-Office Management, Engineering, Food Technology-Chemistry, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 27: Employee Application, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By Carnation Company; Albers Milling Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: The Grocery Products Marketing Organization, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By Carnation Company. Management Development Program. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Ideas Can Bring You Recognition And Reward!, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By Carnation Company. Suggestion submission form. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Carnation Excess Hospital and Medical Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 31: Employee application card, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 32: Employees' Stock Ownership Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 33: Employees' Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 34: Retirement Plan Number One, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 35: Group Insurance Benefits, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 36: Let's Get Acquainted, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 37: Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 38: Hospital And Disability Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 39: Retirement Plan: Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 40: Welcome, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 41: Let's Talk Back!, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By Stanley W. Parsons; Floyd Hill. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: This Is What You Think, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By Carnation Company; Albers Milling Company. Results of 1953 Employee Opinion Poll. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: The Company You Keep, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By Carnation-Albers Sales Organization. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Insurance cards and instructions, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 45: Group Insurance benefits, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 46: Elbridge A. Stuart Scholarships, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
    By Carnation Company Scholarship Foundation. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Employees Suggeston Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 48: Elbridge A. Stuart Scholarships, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Item 49: Vacation Policy for Non-Union, Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Box: 27, Folder: 14 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Apprentice Training, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
    By Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Program of Graduate Study, Publication (Box 27, Folder 14)
    By Carnegie-Illinois Steel Corporation, University of Pittsburgh, Illinois Institute of Technology, and Indiana University. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 15 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Administrative Manual Supervisory, Publication (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Box: 27, Folder: 16 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation Manual, 1937, Publication (Box 27, Folder 16)
    By Industrial Engineering Department. Revised 1942. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 17 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation Manual, 1937, Publication (Box 27, Folder 17)
    By Industrial Engineering Department. Revised 1942. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 18 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The 1947 Agreement: A Conference, Publication (Box 27, Folder 18)
    By Industrial Relations Deparment. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 19 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Executive Training For The Industries, Publication (Box 27, Folder 19)
    By Carnegie Institue of Technology. Bulletin of the Carnegie Institute fo Technology, series 12:no.8 (1917:May). Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 20 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: A Story of Service On Specialty Steels, Publication (Box 27, Folder 20)
    By The Carpenter Steel Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 21 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Communication Methods at Carrier, Publication (Box 27, Folder 21)
    By Stephen Habbe. Reprinted fromNational Industrial Conference Board, Mangement Record, September, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Carrier Suggestion System, Publication (Box 27, Folder 21)
    By Carrier Corportation. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Courier, Publication (Box 27, Folder 21)
    By Carrier Corporation. May 1954. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 22 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: What CESP Can Mean to You, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
    By Carrier Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Employees Security Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Carrier Employees Security Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Item 5: Record of Major Medical Expense, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: Blue Book: An information Manual for the Men and Women of Carrier Corporation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Item 7: Blue Book: An Information Manual For The Men and Women of Carrier Corporation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Item 8: A Report on Alcoholism At Carrier In Syracuse During 1960, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
    By Ian Maclachlan. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Responsibilites of Staff Members, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
    By Carrier Corporation: Personnel Division. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Starting Ticket, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Item 11: Inter-office Letter: Human Relations at Carrier, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
    By Howard M. Dirks. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Inter-office Letter: Human Relations At Carrier, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
    By Cloud Wampler. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: You And Your Job At Carrier: A Blue Book of Information for Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Item 14: Personnel Organization and Administration, Publication (Box 27, Folder 22)
    By Howard Dirks. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 23 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Voluntary Group Accident Insurance For Salaried Employees of Carrier Coporation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
    By Marsh & McLennan, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A NEW Optional Life Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
    By Prudential Insurance Company of America. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Moving Ahead With Carrier Corporation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Item 4: The Two Faces of Janus, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Item 5: Carrier Employees Security Plan: Plan B, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Item 6: Group Insurance Plan: For Salaried Employees, Retirees and Dependents Eligible For Medicare, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Item 7: Group Insurance Plan: Syracuse Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Item 8: Carrier Employees Security Plan: Plan A, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Item 9: Group Insurance Plan: Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Item 10: Growth and Change At Carrier, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Item 11: Salaried Emplyees Benefits, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Item 12: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
    By Elliot Division of Carrier Corporation. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Carrier Group Insurance Plane for Exempt Employees, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Item 14: Carrier Employees: Savings and Investment Plan, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Item 15: Carrier Institute of Business, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
    By Carrier Corporation. Seventh General Session, September 9 to December 2, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Carrier Corporation, Publication (Box 27, Folder 23)
    A study by Harriman, Ripley and Company and Hemphill, Noyes, Graham, Parsons and Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 24 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Mutual Obligations of Labor and Management, Publication (Box 27, Folder 24)
    By Robert N. Denham. Lecture no.9, November 14, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Mutual Obligations of Labor and Management, Publication (Box 27, Folder 24)
    By George W. Taylor. Lecture no.5, October 11, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Mutual Obligations of Labor and Management, Publication (Box 27, Folder 24)
    By Leo Wolman. Lecture no.7, October 20, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Apprenticeship Standars of Carrier Corporation: For Toolmakers and Machinists, Publication (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: Carrier Institute of Business, Publication (Box 27, Folder 24)
    By Carrier Institute of Business. Sixth General Session. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Carrier Institute of Business, Publication (Box 27, Folder 24)
    By Carrier Institute of Business. Seventh General Session. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Carrier Institute of Business, Publication (Box 27, Folder 24)
    By Carrier Institute of Business. Fourth General Session. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Carrier Institute of Business, Publication (Box 27, Folder 24)
    By Carrier Institute of Business. Fifth Advanced Session. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Carrier Institute of Business, Publication (Box 27, Folder 24)
    By Carrier Institute of Business. Fifth General Session. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 25 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Salary Administration Manual, Publication (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Salary Administration Manual, Publication (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Box: 27, Folder: 26 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Employee's Dream Comes True, Publication (Box 27, Folder 26)
    By J. Frank Beaman. Reprinted from The Saturday Evening Post, December 16, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Strike At Carrier: A Documentary, Publication (Box 27, Folder 26)
    Clippings. Item is in English.
- Box: 27, Folder: 27 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Employees' Book on Do's and Don'ts, Publication (Box 27, Folder 27)
    By Carson Pirie Scott and Company. Item is in English.
- Box: 28, Folder: 1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Before the National Labor Board, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
    By John C. Gall; Clark M. Robertson; John F. Lane. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Articles and Regulations, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: National War Labor Board, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Regional War Labot Board, Publication (Box 28, Folder 1)